Don't you move.
Yan 'ai?
Come on, chill.
I know what you're thinking,
that I'm some traitor, right?
But I don't care what
anyone thinks you hear!
When I infiltrated Wrath, I had one goal,
and today's the day I
follow through on it.
The boss will be proud I
carried out his last wish.
What last wish?
Who are you talking about?
It's someone you know very well.
Nobuyuki Sugo.
I'm all confused now.
You said last wish, but he's alive.
He might as well be dead.
He'll be in jail ten years minimum.
But I got off barely.
I played dumb and blamed
everything on a co-worker.
That's how I got away.
Then you were involved with those
experiments he was doing on people.
I wasn't just involved.
My job was to collect the
data from those people.
Yeah, that was fun.
Copping fields with my
virtual tentacles. Oh well,
the boss's research days might be over,
but the connections he made
are all still in place.
I mean, it would be a waste
not to make the most of them.
He'd chew me out and I
wouldn't blame him one bit.
What do you mean, connections?
The National Security Agency of America.
You're saying all this time, you leaked
info about the project to the Americans?
That's right.
And if the ones on board
get their hands on Alice,
they promised me full immunity, a big
fat bonus, and a cushy new job overseas.
It's an American success story
for the ages. The kind Mr.
Sugo always dreamed of.
Kirito's a goner if I don't hurry.
I need to get Rinko's attention.
Don't move!
Oh, I'll take it as much as it won't be.
I won't be able to run
away from the same time.
Look, I won't be able
to get more than once.
I don't know if I'm wrong, but...
I'm not only gonna make a
difference in the world.
I'll take it as much as it can be.
There are no words that
are tied to strong,
strong, strong, strong.
I'm still looking forward
to it, but I can't break it!
What is your soul?
What is it?
I'm still looking forward
to it, but I can't find it.
Oh
Your subtilizer!
I was hoping you'd be Alice.
It doesn't matter.
I'll catch up to her.
You look familiar.
We met before, back in GGO, didn't we?
And if I remember correctly,
your name is Sinon.
Of all places to run into each other.
What do you want?
Why are you here?
It was inevitable our
paths would cross again.
This is what's called fate.
Two people brought together, thanks
to the power of the soul and now!
I'll get to learn a few things like about
the STL and if I can eat real
souls with it, like I can!
fluct lights even better i'll learn
what i couldn't when i killed you
in b .o .b how sweet your soul
really is your soul
will be so sweet
No.
What is this?
I can't fight it.
Xenon, when I picked the name Sutilizer,
I wanted it to define everything I am.
I'm ingenious, elusive,
refined, insidious like a thief.
I've stolen your will to fight,
and now I'll steal your soul.
No, I can't let know.
I won't let you.
Stop it.
What the...
It's the Electrode.
But what's it doing here?
Kirito, you went and saved me again.
All right, I can do this.
You're definitely not a god or a devil.
You're a plain old human.
Don't miss!
Don't miss, Hecate!
Now we're talking.
Keep fighting!
Protect the people of the Underworld!
Don't light up!
Have mercy!
Someone, help us! Listen up!
We'll punch a hole through the enemy line!
Bellflower team, Lily team,
push them to the right!
Stay close!
Sink your sword skills. Ready?
In five, four, three, two...
Don't give up, guys!
We need to keep on busy!
Rue!
I'm done.
Get back, Sakuya!
Leave her alone!
I have to do something.
I can't just stand here.
There's only one way to
get our point across.
Isn't that right, Yuki?
Everyone, listen!
I need to get through here!
Clear a space for me!
You got it!
Techi, Tolkien, Nori!
Let's sync up our attacks
and knock him back!
In three, two, hit it!
Listen to me.
You've all been deceived.
This server belongs to a Japanese
company, and these people are not hackers.
We are legitimate users. You're lying.
We saw what you did.
When we logged in, you were
killing Red Knights left and right.
They were the same as us!
We were defending ourselves against them!
They were American players
who were also deceived!
You're all being used to
sabotage this server! Think!
Where does all this rage
and hatred for us come from?
It's not you!
Someone put you up to this!
Hey, are you telling us the truth?
My handle's Moonphase. And what's yours?
I go by Suyune.
Alright.
I believe you.
Ever since I dove in here, I
had a bad feeling about this.
Excuse me. Let me buy.
Moonphase.
There you are.
Something's way off
about this game. Mishang.
You think so too, huh? Yeah.
The message we got said that hackers
from Japan were the aggressors here.
But by the looks of it, all you guys
are doing is protecting each other.
Thank goodness you believe us. Hang on.
Do you have any kind of proof
what you're saying's true?
What the hell are you
doing talking to them?
The last thing we need
in our ranks is traitors!
Y 'all know how the Japanese are.
You can't trust them.
Besides, if this was a Japanese server?
And they're really legit users?
then how come they got
all the high-grade gear?
Huh?
Well, I know.
They cheated like they always
do and stole it from us.
Yeah, you started to totally cheat.
We didn't.
Yes, our gear is different, but that's
because we took our maims from other games!
and we converted them to this world.
Ha, you're telling me.
You're so dumb you'd move
your main character to a
test server you're lying
they're all a bunch of liars!
I'm not I swear please
believe me we knew we might
lose our characters but
our friends they Shut up!
Jesus, Yuna!
Everyone, calm down!
Kill the hackers!
I guess this is it.
Who's that?
Who are they?
We came as fast as we could.
Why are you here?
The Empress said you had
to stand by at the gate.
We're all in this together.
Lil' Pillan, take the
pugilists and fall back.
I'll keep these creeps busy.
But we should fight them with you. No way!
You and your people have suffered
enough casualties already.
Don't you worry.
It doesn't matter how many of them
there are, they're going down.
How's Kirito? Is he stable?
Yeah, so far.
And Higa just got to the panel.
How's the decoy working out?
We threw all the smoke grenades
we had into the corridor.
It's as thick as pea soup right now,
and they're shooting all over the place.
Once that smoke starts clearing
up, we'll have to lock up again.
And that won't be long.
Higa said it's going to take him about
five minutes to connect everyone.
What's this limit opposition quotient
detection threshold report do you know?
What this means oh my god
what's wrong with you there's no
question it's Another flux light
that broke its limits but why
now at a time like this are you
Saying there's another one like
alice in there it's not on the
same level as alice technically
This ai fluctlight broke through
the limits of its emotional
circuits rather than its logical
Circuits no it's heading south
toward that horde of americans
hey kikuoka yes
what is it look it
I found an external command jammed
into the code that looks fishy
Injecting simulated pain
into the right ocular
region why would you put a limitation like
that On the people of the
underworld no we didn't
do that that makes no
sense at all it defeats
the Purpose of the project why it's it's
obviously sabotage yeah
it is in fact it doesn't
look Anything like higa's
coding style here's
a comment about it code
871 what's 871 about?
I have no idea.
It's the first time I'm seeing it.
Actually, hold on.
I have seen it somewhere before.
That's what's-his-name's lab coat.
You know, the guy who went with Higa?
Yuna.
Code 871.
Yuna!
Sorry I wasn't planning
to shoot you I I was just
gonna stall you and destroy
the connector box Then
I was gonna head on over
to the main control room
side and join the others
None of you wrath people
were supposed to die as
long as you didn't get in
the way of us getting It
was supposed to be happy
endings all around Say
what you gotta be kidding
me idiot did you forget
why we climbed down here?
This is our only chance
to get Kirito's mind back.
Kirito's soul
is at stake.
It's your fault if it dies.
Oh, right.
You do have a point there. Mm-hmm.
I don't care.
Let it die.
After all, he did kill someone special.
To me!
He's the one who killed my
precious Admi! Admi? Who?
The pontifex of the Axiom Church!
Her eminence! Administrator!
Add me.
She and I were close.
I promised her I'd give her
total control of the underworld,
and that's just what I did.
Oh, and if the server
ever got reinitialized,
I swore I'd eject her light
cube before she was erased.
You bastard.
You corrupted the underworld.
Sort of.
Although she did make
contact with me first.
I was working late one night, and then
suddenly I heard her voice over the speakers.
Talk about a shock.
She found the entire command
list for the Underworld
all by herself and opened
up a line to our side.
Soon after that, I was using an STL
to dive in and spend time with her.
What a woman.
Her personality, voice, mannerisms.
She was my type in every way imaginable.
And then she promised me something.
If I helped her, I'd be her number
one slave and one day be her king.
I take it back.
He's the one who got corrupted.
But now she's dead.
Murdered by that goddamn punk.
I have to avenge her death,
otherwise she'll never rest in peace.
Someone has to die.
Some one.
Just one person is all.
I'll give her the memorial she deserves.
That's enough.
Stop it. Stop it!
HALT!
I'll get you some help! Just hold on!
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
No, Liz.
Don't say that.
It's not.
Tell your people to
lay down their weapons.
They do that.
And I promise not to
kill you or any of them.
We will not!
We do not fear death!
We shall fight you until the last!
Do what he says and surrender!
It's over!
It's not worth dying for!
I know how you feel, believe me!
You have to survive!
That's why we're here!
It's...
it's our only...
We win!
We beat the hackers!
Been a while.
Lightning flash.
Haven't heard anyone use
that handle in a long time.
God, it sure does bring back
some good memories. Revenge.
Is that it?
You want to punish the Assault Team
for destroying Laughing Coffin?
Are you stupid or something?
Try this on for size.
Remember how someone tipped the Assault
Team off about Laughing Coffin's hideout?
Well, that someone was me!
Why would you do that?
To prove a point.
To make you guys into the
cold-blooded murderers we were.
Specifically your boyfriend.
Always acting high and mighty, but in
the end he's just a killer like me.
You're insane.
That's what you wanted?
To make Kirito - To make him
kill someone in SAO? Yup.
That's exactly what I wanted to do.
That day I found myself a hiding place
and watched the whole thing go down.
when the dumbass in black snapped and
chopped down two of my fellow coffins,
and damn near blew my cover
because I was laughing so hard.
You monster!
Do you know the guilt you made him suffer?
How much he still suffers? Really?
Glad to hear I rubbed off on him, but
I doubt he feels that guilty about it.
If he's all torn up like you say, why,
playing VR games would be the
last thing he'd do, but he does.
Maybe killing those guys was no biggie.
Hey, here's an idea.
Your boy's in here, too, isn't he?
Yeah, let's ask him how he feels.
No, don't! Please!
It's SHOWTIME!
Thank you.
I don't know what to do